jason@jasonbrunelle.com ● (832) 499-1660 ● linkedin.com/in/jason-brunelle-18b6bb177 ● github.com/jasonmb626

SUMMARY

Computer Programmer and Quality Assurance Technician with over 20 years computer experience whose passion for computers never wavered in that time. Experience in Programming, Quality Assurance, and System Administration. Recent graduate with a B.S. in Computer Science with ten years management experience. Dedicated problem-solver, strategic thinker and multi-tasker who keeps calm under pressure.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming/Languages: HTML/CSS/JavaScript, Node.js/Express, React C/C++/C#, Java

Database: MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL, Microsoft SQL Server

Tools: Git/GitHub, Microsoft Office, Windows, Linux

Methodologies: Agile:Scrum

EDUCATION

University Of Houston-Downtown

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Houston Community College

Associate in Arts

January 2016-July 2019 GPA: 3.86

January 2015-May 2016

GPA:4.00

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

General Manager - Landmark Theatres - River Oaks Theatre

July 2009-July 2019

- Maintained a customer-focused atmosphere where team members could all contribute their talents towards excellent guest experiences
- Created/maintained multiple Excel Workbooks (including helping maintain the official corporate audit workbook) used to improve workflow company-wide
- Converted movie trailers to industry-standard digital projection for company-wide use
- Troubleshot physical plant, projection, and point of sale issues, sometimes under pressure because guest experience for large audience was at stake
- o Ensured Payment Card Industry (PCI) compliance
- Utilized interpersonal communication skills with home office employees
- Trained employees and managers for new opens and changes in point-of-sale software

Senior Technician - University of North Texas – Resnet

June 1999-May 2002

- o Implemented a web interface for students to report Internet issues in a pre-framework era
- Implemented the business logic to assign technicians to trouble tickets based on the schedules of the technicians and clients
- Designed security measures for computer labs with software on the front and a backends
- Set up and maintained Linux/Apache/MySQL/PHP servers (with a list of all University residents)

Quality Assurance Engineer - STB/3DFX

June 1998-January 1999

- Tested video card drivers and installation software to ensure quality product
- Communicated with developers to fix bugs and improve the software